nfldraftdog.com 2013-04-11

# Privacy Policy

**Draft Dog** knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Draft Dogs's treatment of personal information that we gather when you are on our website and when you use our services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Draft Dog does not own or control, or to individuals that Draft Dog does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by Draft Dog:  
We do not collect personal information on from our users on our website. We collect the following types of information from our users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Draft Dog and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, your cookie information, and the page you requested. Draft Dog may use this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

Draft Dog may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Draft Dog will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

E-mail Communications

Draft Dog is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. Yardbarker may send out e-mails with football-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Our cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Draft Dog's coolest features.

Draft Dog's advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A's privacy policy and opt-out page.

Sharing Your Information:  
Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

Draft Dog Personnel: Our personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of our business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Draft Dog, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of Draft Dog and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: Draft Dog allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Draft Dog website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.
